// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowecase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'A group of pugs is called this:',
      a: 'pumble',
      b: 'puggle',
      c: 'snuggle',
      d: 'grumble',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The "perfect" pug has this feature (though they are all perfect): ',
      a: 'two curls in their tail',
      b: 'black shadowing near ears',
      c: 'eyes placed 3 inches apart',
      d: 'one large wrinkle',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Pugs are originally from where?',
      a: 'Korea',
      b: 'China',
      c: 'Egypt',
      d: 'Canada',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Pugs are known to have short skulls, and a flat face- the term for this is:',
      a: 'brachycephalic',
      b: 'drachycephalic',
      c: 'resprephalic',
      d: 'short-nose-icitis',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'How long have pugs been around?',
      a: 'Since 400 B.C.',
      b: 'Since 100 B.C.',
      c: 'Since the 1700s',
      d: 'Since the 1500s',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the cutest, bestest, sweetest pug that ever existed?',
      a: 'Doug the Pug',
      b: 'Mr.Pickles the Pug',
      c: 'Frank, from Men in Black',
      d: 'Otis',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'If Mr.Pickles was a type of pickle, he would be this kind: ',
      a: 'Sweet gherkin pickle',
      b: 'Spicy dill',
      c: 'Bread & Butter ',
      d: 'Just a cucumber',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Frank the pug, from Men in Black, is what type of alien? ',
      a: 'Balchinian',
      b: 'Worm',
      c: 'Kylothian',
      d: 'Remoolian',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many pounds overweight is Mr.Pickles?',
      a: 'he is perfect',
      b: '2 lbs',
      c: '5 lbs',
      d: '7 lbs',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Mr.Pickles favorite treat? You can often find Marcus feeding him this.',
      a: 'carrots',
      b: 'bananas',
      c: 'raspberries',
      d: 'blueberries',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};